export const flashcardQuestions = [
  {
    question: "Welcome! Let's get started",
    answer: "Are you ready?"
  },
  {
    question: "What does the color green often symbolize in psychology?",
    answer: "Growth, harmony, freshness, and safety."
  },
  {
    question: "True or False: People are more likely to remember emotionally charged memories than neutral ones.",
    answer: "True"
  },
  {
    question: "What is the 'halo effect' in psychology?",
    answer: "It's a bias where our overall impression of a person influences how we feel and think about their character."
  },
  {
    question: "What is cognitive dissonance?",
    answer: "The mental discomfort experienced when holding two or more conflicting beliefs, values, or attitudes."
  },
  {
    question: "True or False: Multitasking increases productivity.",
    answer: "False. It often reduces efficiency and performance."
  },
  {
    question: "What part of the brain is primarily responsible for decision-making?",
    answer: {src:'prefrontal.avif'}
  },
  {
    question: "What is the 'bystander effect'?",
    answer: "A social psychological theory that individuals are less likely to offer help to a victim when other people are present."
  },
  {
    question: "What is the psychological term for the fear of missing out?",
    answer: "FOMO (Fear of Missing Out)."
  },
  {
    question: "What does the term 'confirmation bias' refer to?",
    answer: "The tendency to search for, interpret, and recall information in a way that confirms oneâ€™s preexisting beliefs or hypotheses."
  },
  {
    question: "How long does it typically take to form a habit, according to research?",
    answer: "On average, about 66 days."
  }
];
